Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Diamond Information Center Vertical File, 1930s-1980s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Vertical File, (78 boxes)
  - 400. Diamond Cutting
    - 422. Cuts & Shapes (general)
      - 422.MAR. Marquise cut (Box 49)
      - 422.MUL. Multiple cuts and trademark cuts (Box 49)
      - 422.OVA. Oval cut (Box 49)
      - 422.PEA. Pear cut (Box 49)
      - 422.PRO. Profile cut (Box 49)
      - 422.QUA. Quadrillion cut (Box 49)
      - 422.ROSE. Rose cut (Box 50)
      - 422.TRI. Trilliant cut (Box 50)
    - 424. Recutting (Box 50)
    - 425. Automatic Diamond Polishing Machine (Box 50)
    - 430. Cutters and Cutting Organizations
      - 430.ASS. Asscher Family (Box 50)
      - 430.BUE. Abel Buell (Box 50)
      - 430.DEH. Bernard de Hann (Box 50)
      - 430.DEM. Demonstrator Cutters (Box 50)
      - 430.DES. Maurice S. Dessau Co. (Box 50)
      - 430.DIN. Dinhofer Diamond Cutting Works (Box 50)
      - 430.KAP. Lazare Kaplan & Sons (Leo & George) (Box 50)
      - 430.KAT. Gustave Katz (Katz Cutting Works) (Box 50)
      - 430.MIS. Miscellaneous Cutters (Box 50)
      - 430.VAN. Van Moppes & Son (Amsterdam cutter) (Box 50)
      - 430.WES. Maurice Westreich (Cutter of MOUW Diamond Cutting Works) (Box 50)
  - 500. Diamond Mines
    - 500. Diamond mining (Box 50)
    - 500. Diamond mining--Methods and chambering (Box 50)
    - 510. Cleaving (Box 50)
    - 510. Diamond Dictionary Research
      - 510.EMJ. Diamond Mining and Recovery (Eng. & Min. Jr. Nov. 1969) (Box 51)
      - 510.HOI. Hoist (Box 51)
      - 510.KIM. Kimberly Mine Museum (Box 51)
    - 511. Open Cast Mining (Box 51)
    - 512. Alluvial Mining (West Africa) (Box 51)
    - 513.Types of mines
      - 513.MOON. Moon Mining Tektites (Box 51)
      - 513.1.(66) Beach Mining .. Marine Diamond Corp at C.D.M., 1966 (Box 51)
      - 513.1.(67) Beach Mining .. Marine Diamond Corp at C.D.M., 1967 (Box 51)
      - 513.1.SEA. Sea Background Material: Sea Mining (Box 51)
      - 513.1.SEA. Sea Diamond Corporation Ltd.: 1964, 1967 Annual Reports (Box 51)
      - 513.2.SEA. Pomona - photos (Sea Mining) (Box 51)
      - 513.3.SEA. Colpontoon - photos (Sea Mining) (Box 51)
      - 513.3. Offshore diamonds (Box 52)
      - 513.4.SEA. Sea barges used in sea mining - photographs (Box 52)
    - 514. Mining Processes
      - 514. Central Recovery Plant at Kimberly for Bultfontein, Dutoitspan, Wesselton mines (Box 52)
      - 514. Mining and cutting photos (Box 52)
      - 514. Ore processing (Box 52)
      - 514. Recovery or pulsator process step-by-step photos (Box 52)
      - 514. Tipping (Box 53)
      - 514. Washing (Box 53)
      - 514.X-Ry. X-Ray Recovery (Box 53)
      - [515. Shipping and Sorting Processes]
        - 515. Crushing (Box 53)
        - 515.SHI. Diamond shipping (Box 53)
        - 515. Sorting .. De Beers (Box 53)
        - 515. Central sorting office .. photos (Box 53)
    - 516. World Diamond Production Statistics
      - 516. Production statistics - 1971 (Box 53)
      - 516.JCK. Diamond production (JCK annual story) (Box 53)
      - 516.WPF. World Production Figures - 1968 (confidential) (Box 53)
      - 516.1969. World Diamond Production - 1969 (Box 53)
    - 517. De Beers Mine hostels (Box 53)
    - 520. Diamond Mining Areas
      Arranged alphabetically by geographic location.
      - 520.ANG. Angola (Box 53)
      - 520.ANT. Diamond Mining in Antarctic (Box 53)
      - 520.BEL. Belgian Congo (Box 53)
      - 520.BRA. Brazil (Box 53)
      - 520. Diamond mining in Canada (Box 53)
      - 520.CON. Congo (Box 53)
      - 520.GOL. Golconda, India (Box 53)
      - 520.IND. India (Box 53)
      - 520.KOS. Kostern, Western Transvaal (Box 53)
      - 520.LIC. Lichtenburg District (Box 53)
      - 520. Meteorites .. Diamonds in ... (Box 53)
      - 520.NAMA. Namaqualand Diamonds (Box 53)
      - 520.RHO. Rhodesia (Box 53)
      - 520.RUS. Russian - mining area (Box 53)
      - 520.SIE. Sierra Leone (Box 53)
      - 520.KIM. Kimberley Town [South Africa] photographs (Box 53)
      - 520.SLE. Sierra Leone mining area (Box 54)
      - 520. Mining areas .. South America (Box 54)
      - 520.SPA. Diamonds found in Spain (Box 54)
      - 520.U.S. Mining in the U.S. (Box 54)
      - 520. Vall River Mining (Box 54)
      - 520.VEN. Venezuela (Box 54)
      - 520. West Coast Mining, photos (Box 54)
    - 530. Individual Diamond Mines
      Arranged alphabetically by name of mine.
      - 530.BAR. Barkly West (Box 54)
      - 530.BUL. Bulfontein Mine (Box 54)
      - [530.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of Southwest Africa]
        - 530.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of Southwest Africa (Box 54)
        - 530.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of Southwest Africa, before 1967 (Box 54)
        - 530.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of Southwest Africa, 1967 photos (Box 54)
        - 530.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of Southwest Africa, 1971 photos (Box 54)
      - [530.DEB. De Beers Mine]
        - 530.DEB. De Beers Mine (Box 55)
        - 530.DEB. De Beers Original Mine, 1872 (Box 55)
        - 530.DEB. De Beers Mines (early scenes) (Box 55)
        - 530.DEB. De Beers - Debswana's mines Jwaneng (Box 55)
        - 530.DEB. De Beers .. Mining Blueground (Box 55)
        - 530.DEB.IND. De Beers Industrial Corp. Lit. Ann. Rep., 1965-1967 (Box 55)
      - 530.DUT. Dutoitspan Mine (Box 55)
      - 530.DUT. Workers and housing conditions at Dutoitspan Mine (Box 55)
      - 530.F. Finsch Mine, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 55)
      - 530.F. Finsch Mine, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 56)
      - 530.GOL. Golconda Mine (Box 56)
      - 530.GUY. Guyana (Box 56)
      - 530.IND. India (Box 56)
      - 530.JAG. Jagersfontein Mine (Box 56)
      - [530.KIM. Kimberley Mine]
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley Mine, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 56)
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley Mine, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 57)
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley Mine (early photos) (Box 57)
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley Mine (today -- photos) (Box 58)
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley (Diamond Centenary Celebration photos) (Box 58)
        - 530.KIM. Kimberley Mine (written material) (Box 58)
      - 530.KLE. Kleinzee Plant (Box 58)
      - 530.KOF. Koffiefontein Mine (Box 58)
      - 530.KOF. Koffiefontein Mine - photos (Box 58)
      - 530.LES. Lesotho Mine (Box 58)
      - 530.LIC. Lichtenburg Diggings (Box 58)
      - 530.MUR. Murfreesboro, Arkansas mine (Box 58)
      - 530.MWA. Mwadui (Box 58)
      - 530.NOO. Nooitgedacht (Box 58)
      - 530.O. Orapa Mine, Botswana (background material) (Box 58)
      - 530.O. Orapa Mine, Botswana (photographs) (Box 59)
      - 530.PRE-PREM. Premier Mines, (2 folders) (Box 59)
      - 530.PRE. Premier annual reports (Box 59)
      - 530.WES. Wesselton Mine (Box 60)
      - 530.WIL. Williamson Mines (Box 60)
    - 530. Anita Viksne/Barbara Gleason, South African photos (Box 60)
    - 531.SA. South Africa jewelry designers (Box 60)
    - [540-542. Mining Companies]
      - 540. American Brazilian Investment Co. (George Bruce, Atlanta) (Box 60)
      - 540.CHA. Chamber of Mines of S.A. [South Africa] (Box 60)
      - 540.CHA. Jack Chapman .. De Beers employee (Box 60)
      - 540.COR. Diamond finder .. J.O. Cornelissen .. (Box 60)
      - 540.KLA. Klaas Mosekimang .. worker diamond finder (Box 60)
      - 540.SIM. Simon Lugulwana (Box 60)
      - 541.BAR. Barney Barnato (Box 60)
      - 541.RHO. Cecil J. Rhodes (Box 60)
      - 541.RUS. Maurice Rush, Ex. Dir. Anglo Am. (Box 60)
      - 542.CDM. Consolidated Diamond Mines of South-west Africa, Ltd.: annual reports (Box 60)
      - 542.DEB. De Beers Mining Company
        - 542.DEB. De Beers Company (miscellaneous) (Box 60)
        - 542.DEB. De Beers Consolidated Mines: annual reports (Box 60)
        - 542.DEB. De Beers Consolidated Mines (to 1900) (Box 61)
        - 542.DEB. Harry Oppenheimer's Industrial Africa, Fortune, May 1960 (Box 61)
        - 543.DEB. De Beers Consolidated Mines: 1965 Mining Annual Review (Box 61)
  - 600. Industrial Diamonds
    - 621. Metal working (Box 61)
    - 621. X-Ray orientation of diamonds for diamond tools (Box 61)
    - 622.C&C. Industrial diamonds in concrete and construction (Box 61)
    - 623.CER. Industrial diamonds in the ceramics industry (Box 61)
    - 623.CER. Industrial diamonds in the stone industry (Box 61)
    - 624.GLA. Industrial diamonds in the glass industry (Box 61)
    - 626.OCA. Other cutting application: plastics and rubber (Box 61)
    - 627.NCU. Non-cutting uses of industrial diamonds (Box 61)
    - 630.GD. Diamond grinding (Box 61)
    - 630.IDR. Industrial research: De Beers (Box 61)
    - 650.IDC. Industrial Diamond Congress (Paris, May 1962) (Box 61)
    - 660.M&RD. Mining and recovery of industrial diamonds (Box 61)
  - 700. General Diamond Information
    - 700.CAR. Carats (Box 61)
    - 700.GEN. General diamond information: investment (Box 61)
    - 711. Hardness of diamonds (Box 61)
    - 711. The physics of diamond (Box 61)
    - [712. Color]
      - 712. Color in diamonds (Box 61)
      - 712.1. Color in diamonds .. natural, (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - 712.2. Color in diamonds .. treated (Box 62)
    - 713. Gemprint (Box 62)
    - 720.M. Diamonds on the moon (Box 62)
    - [721?]. Objects d'Art (Box 62)
    - [730-739. General Information (Print and Multimedia Resources)]
      - 730.CUS. U.S. Customs: history and general information (Box 62)
      - 730. Composition of Diamond (CU [Consumers Union] article), 1950 (Box 62)
      - 730. Federal Trade Commission rulings (Box 62)
      - 730.PUB. Publicity, early history: De Beers Mines (Box 62)
      - 731. Books ... for Jewelers (Box 63)
      - 731.CHA. Sally Chase (Box 63)
      - 731.CVA. .. Diamonds all over the world (Box 63)
      - 731. Occurrence mining and recovery of diamonds by Lindolm [empty folder] (Box 63)
      - [732. Print Articles and Photographs]
        - 732.BAL. How Diamonds Reach You, by Iain Balfour (Box 63)
        - 732.BARRON'S. Not Just for the Carriage Trade, Barron's (Box 63)
        - 732. Diamonds, by Stewart Robertson, Family Circle, October 1946 [empty folder] (Box 63)
        - 732. But What Does a Diamond Do For You, by H. Market in Family Circle, June 1967 [empty folder] (Box 63)
        - 732. Article, Diamonds Hands & Hearts, for Lady Beautiful (Box 63)
        - 732. Review of The History of Diamond Production and the Diamond Trade (Box 63)
        - 732. Diamonds .. Geographical Magazine, June 1965 (Box 63)
        - 732. For Forbes article on diamonds [empty folder] (Box 63)
        - 732.1. Forbes Four Hundred (Box 63)
        - [732]. Diamond bibliography (Box 63)
        - 732. Capsule History of Diamonds, Holiday, June 1965 (Box 63)
        - 732.EOH. Diamonds Are Big Business, E.O. Hauser (Box 63)
        - 732. Exploring the World of Gems (Box 63)
        - 732.FIR. First Thing for the Third Finger, article for Dell Publishing .. wedding book (Box 63)
        - 732.GEN. Diamond articles -- general (Box 63)
        - 732.GGR. South Africa's King of Diamonds, Reader's Digest, 1964 (Box 63)
        - 732.GUY. Three Quarters of a Century in the Diamond Trade, by Guy Young, March 1962 (Box 63)
        - 732.HAN. Diamond Mining & Recovery Today, Gems and Gemology, 1963. (Box 63)
        - 732.HOW. How to Buy a Diamond, Bride and Home, 1959 (Box 63)
        - 732.KEL. The Lapidary of the Learned King (Box 63)
        - 732.MBC. .. How to Tell Gems from Junk, Murray Boltinoff, Cue, 7 February 1953 (Box 63)
        - 732.MCL. Diamonds Are a Girl's Most Overpriced Friend, Joe McCarthy, McCall's, March 1969 (Box 63)
        - 732.MIN. Minerals Quarterly, (2 folders) (Box 63)
        - 732. Nervous Ice .. Saturday Evening Post, 1941 (Box 63)
        - 732.NY. Diamond, by Emily Hahn, New Yorker, 1956 (Box 63)
        - [732]. Diamonds Linked to Earth Eruptions, New York Times, March 1973 (Box 63)
        - 732.PAR. Paris Match (Box 63)
        - 732.SWI. The Many Sided Diamond, by George S. Switzer, National Geographic, 1958 (Box 63)
        - 732.WARD. Fred Ward article/photos, National Geographic, January 1979, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - [733. Television]
        - 733.ABC. Diamonds, John Gunther, The High Road, ABC TV, 26 December 1959 (Box 64)
        - 733.BC. King of Diamonds, Broderick Crawford (never produced) (Box 64)
      - [734. Film]
        - 734. A Diamond is Forever - film (Box 64)
        - 734. Films .. on diamonds (Box 64)
        - 734. The Eternal Gem - film (Box 64)
      - 736. Willems catalog of books about gems (Box 64)
      - [737. Lectures]
        - 737.HAN. 1950 tour, B.G. Hannaford (many photos of mining steps) (Box 64)
        - 737.HAN. Women lecturers (Box 64)
        - 737.VER. Infinite Versatility of Jewelry, slide lecture, 1969 (Box 64)
        - 737.WHI. Lecture on diamonds (industrial), Bill Whitehead (Box 64)
    - 741. Diamonds in songs (Box 65)
    - [750. Holiday Themes]
      - 750.APR. April .. Diamond Month (Box 65)
      - 750.CHR. Christmas (Box 65)
      - 750.EAS. Easter (Box 65)
      - 750. Gift books (Box 65)
      - 750.LEA. Leap Year (Box 65)
      - 750.SAD. Sadie Hawkins Day (Box 65)
      - 750.VAL. Valentine (Box 65)
    - 751. Jubilees (Box 65)
    - 760. Oddities in diamonds (Box 66)
    - 771. Postage stamps with diamonds (Box 66)
    - 772. Prizes, diamonds (Box 66)
    - 780. Diamonds at ascot (Box 66)
  - 800. Miscellaneous (jewelry)
    - 811. Lazered diamonds (Box 66)
    - 811.DIAM. Diamonair (simulated diamonds) Airtron division, Litton Industries, Saks Fifth Avenue (Box 66)
    - 811. General Electric--Industrial (Box 66)
    - 811. General Electric Synthetic (gem diamond) (Box 66)
    - 811.LIP. Lipsitz diamond (phony) (Box 66)
    - 811. Simulated diamonds, (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - 811. Wellington (Box 67)
    - 812.1.CHA. Chatham emeralds (Box 67)
    - 812.2.HOPE. Hope Star sapphire (syn) (Box 67)
    - 812.3.KAS. Kashan ruby (Box 67)
    - 813. Costume jewelry (Box 67)
    - 813. Swarovski Awards (Box 67)
    - 820. Colored stone jewelry (Box 67)
    - 820.BUR. Burma (booklet: Gem Hunting in Burma) (Box 67)
    - 821. Linde Stars (synthetic emeralds) (Box 67)
    - 822. Pearls (Box 67)
    - 830.GEM. Gemstones (other than diamonds) (Box 67)
    - 830. Birthstones (Box 68)
    - 830.PER. Peridot and sinhalite (Box 68)
    - 830.TAN. Tanzanite (Box 68)
  - 900. Miscellaneous (non-jewelry)
    - 910. Fashions--general
      - 911.1. General history--fashion (Box 68)
      - 911.1.1. Old fashion plates (Box 68)
      - 911.1.45-70. Fashion notes, 1945-1970, (10 folders) (Box 68)
    - 911.2. Fashion Trends and Influences
      - 911.2.ANA. Anatomy influencing fashion (Box 68)
      - 911.2.0.DEC. Decline of haute couture (Box 68)
      - 911.2.1. Nude look (Box 68)
      - 911.2.3. Hemlines (Box 68)
      - 911.2.4. Hotpants (Box 68)
      - 911.2.4. Pants (Box 68)
      - 911.2.5. Sleeves (Box 68)
      - 911.2.6. One shoulder look (Box 68)
      - 911.2.7. Discotheque fashions, 1964-1965 (Box 68)
      - 911.2.7. Blouses, 1947-1949 (Box 69)
      - 911.2.8. Art and fashion (Box 69)
      - 911.2.9. Chemise, 1958-1959, 1972 (Box 69)
      - 911.2.10. Empire trend (Box 69)
      - 911.2.11. New Look - down to the ankles (Box 69)
      - 911.2.12. Fashion fads (Box 69)
    - 911.3. Fashion Showings
      - 911.3.1. Annual fashion showings--American, 1960-1963, (4 folders) (Box 69)
      - 911.3.1. Annual fashion showings--American, 1964-1967, (4 folders) (Box 69)
      - 911.3.1. Annual fashion showings--American, 1968-1970, (3 folders) (Box 70)
      - 911.3.2. Annual fashion showings--European, 1945-1968, (10 folders) (Box 70)
      - 911.3.2. Annual fashion showings--European, 1969-1970, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - 911.3.3. Fashion--Post-War Paris (Box 71)
      - 911.3.3. Paris--Postwar America getting back in step with Paris (Box 71)
      - 911.3.4. Italy--Fashions (Box 71)
      - 911.3.5. White House Fashion Show (first) (Box 71)
      - 911.3.6. United Kingdom--Designers (Box 71)
      - 911.3.7. Eastern Influences, 1965- (Box 71)
    - 911.4. Museum Fashion Collections
      - 911.4. Museum fashion collections [general] (Box 71)
      - 911.4. Smithsonian (Box 71)
    - 911.5. Fashion Retailing
      - 911.5.1. Stores (Box 71)
    - 911.6. Fashion awards
      - 911.6.1. Coty Awards (Box 71)
      - 911.6.2. Neiman Marcus Awards (Box 71)
    - 911.7. Fashion Publications
      - 911.7.1. Publications (Box 71)
      - 911.7.3. Photographers (Box 71)
    - 911.8. Fashion Terminology
      - 911.8.1. Color titles and color reproduction (Box 71)
    - [912. Clothing and Accessories]
      - 912.1. Evening Wear
        - 912.1.1. Formal evening wear, 1945-1953 (Box 71)
        - 912.1.2. Informal evening wear, 1945-1957 (Box 72)
      - 912.2. Streetwear
        - 912.2.2. Sportswear (Box 72)
      - [912.3. Outerwear]
        - 912.3.1. Furs, 1948-1959 (Box 72)
        - 912.3.2. Rainwear, 1956- (Box 73)
      - [912.4. Head Ornamentation]
        - 912.4.1. Hats, 1945- (Box 73)
        - 912.4.2. Scarves [and] babushkas (Box 73)
        - 912.4.3. Headbands (Box 73)
        - 912.4.4. Ribbons (Box 73)
        - 912.4.5. Wigs (Box 73)
        - 912.4.6. Snoods (Box 73)
        - 912.4.7. Hoods (Box 73)
      - 912.5. Underwear (Box 73)
      - [912.6. Clothing Accessories]
        - 912.6.1. Shoes - boots (Box 73)
        - 912.6.1. Shoes (Box 73)
        - 912.6.1. Shoes and boots .. footwear (Box 73)
        - 912.6.2. Hosiery (Box 73)
        - 912.6.3. Gloves (Box 73)
        - 912.6.4. Belts .. the waist (Box 73)
        - 912.6.4. Belts (Box 73)
        - 912.6.5. Eyeglasses (Box 73)
        - 912.6.6. Fans (Box 74)
        - 912.6.7. Tassels (Box 74)
        - 912.6.9. Eyebrow pencil (Box 74)
        - 912.6.10. Handbags (Box 74)
        - 912.6.11. Shawls (Box 74)
        - 912.6.12. Umbrellas (Box 74)
    - [913. Couture]
      - 913.1.1. Best dressed models and best dressed women (Box 74)
      - 913.2.1. New York Couture Council (Box 74)
      - 913.2.2. New York Fashion Group (Box 74)
      - 913.3 Individual Couturiers and Designers
        - 913.3.AAA. Fashion designers (in groups) (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Balenciaga (Box 74)
        - 913.3. BAM. [Balmain, Pierre] (Box 74)
        - 913.3. BEA. [Beene, Geoffrey] (Box 74)
        - 913.3. BLA. [Blass, Bill] (Box 74)
        - 913.3.BRO. [Brooks, Donald] (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Burke-Amey (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Cardin, [Pierre] (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Cassini, Oleg (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Chanel (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Chapman, Ceil (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Courreges (Box 74)
        - 913.3. De La Renta, Oscar (Box 74)
        - 913.3.DIG. Marion Digney (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Dior, Christian (New Look, 1946: Bohan, Dior) (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Estevez, Louis (Box 74)
        - 913.3.FAT. Fath, Jacques (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Fontayne (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Fox, Seymour (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Galanos, James (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Gardin, Annemarie (Box 74)
        - 913.3. Gernreich, Rudi (Box 75)
        - 913.3.GIV. Givenchy, Hubert de (Paris designer) (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Halley, George (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Heim, Jacques (Box 75)
        - 913.3. James, Charles (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Kleibacker, Charles (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Lucille .. Lady Duff Gordon (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Luksus, Tzaims (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Mainbocher (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Molyneux, Edward (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Moore, John (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Norell, Norman (Box 75)
        - 913.3.PAT. Patou, Jean (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Pertigaz (Spain) (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Quant, Mary (London) (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Quirk, Barbara (Box 75)
        - 913.3.RIC. Ricci, Nina (Box 75)
        - 913.3.ROD. Rodrigues, (2 folders) (Box 75)
        - 913.3.RU. Rouff, Maggy (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Sarmi, Nando (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Scaasi, Arnold (Box 75)
        - 913.3. Sharaff, Irene (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Simpson, Adele (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Stavropoulos, George (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Tiffeau, Jacques (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Trigere, Pauline (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Valentina (Box 76)
        - 913.3.WOR. Worth, designer (Box 76)
        - 913.3. Zuckerman, Ben (Box 76)
      - 913.4.CUS. Mildred Custin (Box 76)
    - 913.5.SIN. Singer sewing machines (Box 76)
    - 914.1. Fabrics and textiles (Box 76)
    - 914.4. Buttons (Box 76)
    - 915. Individual hairstyles (Box 76)
    - 916. Makeup trends
      - 916.2. Cosmetics (Box 76)
    - [917. Brides and Weddings]
      - 917.1.CUS. Bridal customs (Box 77)
      - 917.1. Bridal customs and etiquette (Box 77)
      - 917.1.WED. Wedding etiquette (Box 77)
      - 917.2. Bridal fashions (Box 77)
      - 917.2. War brides (Box 77)
      - 917.3. Bridal services (Box 77)
      - 917.7.2. Individual editors and writers (Box 77)
    - 920. Men's clothing (Box 77)
    - 925. Accessories for men .. jewelry (Box 77)
    - 930.C. Consolidated Gold Fields, Ltd. (Box 77)
    - 933. Anglo American Corporation of South Africa, Ltd.
      - 933. Anglo American Corporation of South Africa, Limited (Box 78)
      - 933. Anglo American Annual Report, 1965 (Box 78)
      - 933.AAC. Anglo American Corp. of South Africa - annual reports (Box 78)
      - 933.AAI. Anglo-American Industrial Corporation (Box 78)
      - 933.ANG. Anglo American Corp. (Box 78)
      - 933.ANG. Anglo-American Corp. 50th anniversary, Optima, September 1967 (Box 78)
      - 933.ANG. Anglo-American Corporation, 1969 Annual Report (Box 78)
    - 934. Oppenheimer Hospital (Box 78)
    - 940.1. Fashion, influenced by economy (Box 78)
    - 941. South Africa economic data (Box 78)
    - 941.1.SA. South Africa (Box 78)